{
  "hard": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "Manchester United won their first European Cup/Champions League in 1968. But which Maltese football team did they beat in the first round 4-0 on aggregate?",
      "option_a": "Hibernians",
      "option_b": "Mosta",
      "option_c": "Qormi",
      "option_d": "Floriana",
      "correct": "Hibernians"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "During the 1991 European Cup winner's cup success, United played one team from the English league during the campaign. Who were they?",
      "option_a": "Stockport",
      "option_b": "Fulham",
      "option_c": "Crystal Palace",
      "option_d": "Wrexham",
      "correct": "Wrexham"
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "Who were the Reds playing when Nicky Butt was dismissed for the first time in senior competition, in January 1996?",
      "option_a": "Derby County",
      "option_b": "Newcastle United",
      "option_c": "Liverpool",
      "option_d": "West Ham United",
      "correct": "West Ham United"
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "Crompton, Carey, Aston (Sr), Anderson, Chilton, Cockburn, Delaney, Morris, Pearson, Mitton. Which of the following also started the 1948 FA Cup final for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Jack Warner",
      "option_b": "Jack Rowley",
      "option_c": "Laurie Cassidy",
      "option_d": "Harry Worrall",
      "correct": "Jack Rowley"
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "The match immediately after Sir Matt Busby's death in 1994 was a home game against Everton, which United won 1-0. Who scored the winning goal?",
      "option_a": "Lee Sharpe",
      "option_b": "Roy Keane",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Brian McClair",
      "correct": "Ryan Giggs"
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "Who was the United manager when Sir Bobby Charlton ended his Old Trafford career?",
      "option_a": "Dave Sexton",
      "option_b": "Tommy Docherty",
      "option_c": "Wilf McGuinness",
      "option_d": "Frank O'Farrell",
      "correct": "Tommy Docherty"
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Schmeichel, Keane, Bruce, Pallister, Irwin, Kanchelskis, Ince, Giggs, Cole, Hughes. Which of the following also started the 9-0 win over Ipswich for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_b": "Lee Sharpe",
      "option_c": "Brian McClair",
      "option_d": "Gary Walsh",
      "correct": "Brian McClair"
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "United's record win in the FA Cup is an 8-0 win over Yeovil Town. What year was that?",
      "option_a": "1949",
      "option_b": "1956",
      "option_c": "1963",
      "option_d": "1967",
      "correct": "1949"
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "Van Der Sar, Brown, Ferdinand, Heinze, Ronaldo, Fletcher, Carrick, Giggs, Rooney, Smith. Name the missing player who started United's record 7-1 win in the Champions League?",
      "option_a": "Patrice Evra",
      "option_b": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_c": "Kieran Richardson",
      "option_d": "John O'Shea",
      "correct": "John O'Shea"
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Although 7-1 is United's Champions League record win, it is not their biggest European win. Which Belgian club did it come against and what was the score?",
      "option_a": "FC Basel (9-2)",
      "option_b": "Anderlecht (10-0)",
      "option_c": "Inter Grasshopper Club ZÃ¼rich (15-0)",
      "option_d": "BSC Young Boys (13-1)",
      "correct": "Anderlecht (10-0)"
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "In the 3 seasons he was at Manchester United, how many goals did Jesper Blomqvist score?",
      "option_a": "1",
      "option_b": "2",
      "option_c": "3",
      "option_d": "0",
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "There have only been nine transfers between Manchester United and their heated rivals Liverpool. When was the last time a transfer bwteeen these two clubs happened?",
      "option_a": "1929",
      "option_b": "1964",
      "option_c": "1954",
      "option_d": "1938",
      "correct": "1964"
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "Which one of these teams does NOT share the record for heaviest defeat of Manchester United with 7-0?",
      "option_a": "Blackburn Rovers",
      "option_b": "Aston Villa",
      "option_c": "Wolverhampton Wanderers",
      "option_d": "Birmingham City",
      "correct": "Birmingham City"
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "Schmeichel, Irwin, P Neville, Keane, Pallister, Cantona, Beckham, Cole, Butt, Giggs. Which of the following also started the 1996 FA Cup final for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "David May",
      "option_b": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_c": "Paul Parker",
      "option_d": "Gary Neville",
      "correct": "David May"
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "What was the first ever number worn by Eric Cantona for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "7",
      "option_b": "10",
      "option_c": "12",
      "option_d": "14",
      "correct": "12"
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "Where in the table did Manchester United finish in Sir Alex Ferguson's first full season at the club?",
      "option_a": "11th",
      "option_b": "2nd",
      "option_c": "4th",
      "option_d": "7th",
      "correct": "2nd"
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "Manchester United's first full league campaign in the top flight of English football was in the 1892-1893 season. What position did they finish that year?",
      "option_a": "1st",
      "option_b": "5th",
      "option_c": "16th",
      "option_d": "8th",
      "correct": "16th"
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "Schmeichel, G Neville, Johnsen, May, P Neville, Keane, Beckham, Scholes, Cole, Giggs. Which of the following also started the 1999 FA Cup final for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Denis Irwin",
      "option_b": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_c": "Jaap Stam",
      "option_d": "Teddy Sheringham",
      "correct": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer"
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "question": "Paul Scholes made his debut on 21st September 1994. Who was it against?",
      "option_a": "Ipswich Town",
      "option_b": "Queens Park Rangers",
      "option_c": "Coventry City",
      "option_d": "Port Vale",
      "correct": "Port Vale"
    },
    {
      "number": 20,
      "question": "1974-75: which team did United draw 2-2 against to confirm their second division championship and promotion back to the top flight?",
      "option_a": "Portsmouth",
      "option_b": "Notts County",
      "option_c": "Leyton Orient",
      "option_d": "Bristol Rovers",
      "correct": "Notts County"
    },
    {
      "number": 21,
      "question": "Which club did Frank O'Farrell leave to become United manager?",
      "option_a": "Chelsea",
      "option_b": "Leicester City",
      "option_c": "Arsenal",
      "option_d": "Everton",
      "correct": "Leicester City"
    },
    {
      "number": 22,
      "question": "Wayne Rooney scored a hat-trick on his Manchester United debut, which was a Champions League match. Which other player scored a hat-trick on his Manchester United debut?",
      "option_a": "Robin Van Persie",
      "option_b": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_c": "Charles Sagar",
      "option_d": "Paul Scholes",
      "correct": "Charles Sagar"
    },
    {
      "number": 23,
      "question": "From which club was Irish international Denis Irwin signed from?",
      "option_a": "Derby County",
      "option_b": "Leeds United",
      "option_c": "Oldham Athletic",
      "option_d": "West Bromwich Albion",
      "correct": "Oldham Athletic"
    },
    {
      "number": 24,
      "question": "Denis Law has enjoyed a number of hat-tricks as a Manchester United player. Against how many different teams did he score a hat-trick?",
      "option_a": "15",
      "option_b": "16",
      "option_c": "17",
      "option_d": "18",
      "correct": "18"
    },
    {
      "number": 25,
      "question": "After winning the European Cup in 1968, who did Man Utd play in the World Club Championship the following year?",
      "option_a": "Vasco Da Gama",
      "option_b": "Estudiantes",
      "option_c": "Santos",
      "option_d": "River Plate",
      "correct": "Estudiantes"
    },
    {
      "number": 26,
      "question": "Wayne Rooney's last Champions League goal for Manchester United came against which club?",
      "option_a": "CSKA Moscow",
      "option_b": "Club Brugge",
      "option_c": "Bayer Leverkusen",
      "option_d": "Braga",
      "correct": "CSKA Moscow"
    },
    {
      "number": 27,
      "question": "Of Wayne Rooney's 34 Champions League goals for Manchester united, how many were scored against Italian clubs?",
      "option_a": "5",
      "option_b": "8",
      "option_c": "3",
      "option_d": "10",
      "correct": "10"
    },
    {
      "number": 28,
      "question": "Who holds the record for most consecutive league appearances for United?",
      "option_a": "Joe Jordan",
      "option_b": "Denis Law",
      "option_c": "Steve Coppell",
      "option_d": "Ryan Giggs",
      "correct": "Steve Coppell"
    },
    {
      "number": 29,
      "question": "United have won the Charity Shield 21 times. How many times have they shared it?",
      "option_a": "0",
      "option_b": "2",
      "option_c": "4",
      "option_d": "6",
      "correct": "4"
    },
    {
      "number": 30,
      "question": "Of United's top four record goalscorers, who scored the most in the FA Cup?",
      "option_a": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_b": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
      "option_c": "Denis Law",
      "option_d": "Jack Rowley",
      "correct": "Denis Law"
    },
    {
      "number": 31,
      "question": "Of United's top ten record goalscorers, who has the most goals in the League Cup?",
      "option_a": "Dennis Viollet",
      "option_b": "Jack Rowley",
      "option_c": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_d": "Mark Hughes",
      "correct": "Mark Hughes"
    },
    {
      "number": 32,
      "question": "Against which team did David Beckham score his first Champions League goal for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Rapid Wein",
      "option_b": "Brondby",
      "option_c": "Galatasaray",
      "option_d": "Croatia Zagreb",
      "correct": "Galatasaray"
    },
    {
      "number": 33,
      "question": "Schmeichel, Martin, Irwin, Bruce, Pallister, Kanchelskis, Ince, McClair, Hughes, Blackmore. Which of the following also started the 1991 European Super Cup final for United?",
      "option_a": "Mal Donaghy",
      "option_b": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_c": "Neil Webb",
      "option_d": "Mark Robins",
      "correct": "Neil Webb"
    },
    {
      "number": 34,
      "question": "Sealey, Irwin, Blackmore, Bruce, Pallister, Robson, Ince, McClair, Hughes, Sharpe. Who else started the 1991 European Cup-Winners Cup Final?",
      "option_a": "Neil Webb",
      "option_b": "Mark Robins",
      "option_c": "Danny Wallace",
      "option_d": "Mike Phelan",
      "correct": "Mike Phelan"
    },
    {
      "number": 35,
      "question": "Which team finished runners-up to United in the 1966-67 First Division season?",
      "option_a": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_b": "Leeds United",
      "option_c": "Nottingham Forest",
      "option_d": "Stoke City",
      "correct": "Nottingham Forest"
    },
    {
      "number": 36,
      "question": "Manchester United beat which Polish team in the Quarter-Final on the way to winning the 1968 European Cup?",
      "option_a": "LKS Lodz",
      "option_b": "Polonia Warsaw",
      "option_c": "Legia Warsaw",
      "option_d": "GÃ³rnik Zabrze",
      "correct": "GÃ³rnik Zabrze"
    },
    {
      "number": 37,
      "question": "Van Der Sar, Ferdinand, Vidic, Evra, Ji-Sung, Carrick, Anderson, Ronaldo, Tevex, Rooney. Who else started the 1-0 win against LDU Quito in the 2008 FIFA Club World Cup?",
      "option_a": "Darren Fletcher",
      "option_b": "Jonny Evans",
      "option_c": "Gary Neville",
      "option_d": "Rafael Da Silva",
      "correct": "Rafael Da Silva"
    },
    {
      "number": 38,
      "question": "Van Der Gouw, G Neville, Stam, Berg, P Neville, Beckham, Keane, Scholes, Cole, Solskjaer. Who else started the 1-0 loss to Lazio in the 1999 UEFA Super Cup?",
      "option_a": "Teddy Sheringham",
      "option_b": "Dwight Yorke",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Jordi Cruyff",
      "correct": "Teddy Sheringham"
    },
    {
      "number": 39,
      "question": "Against which team did United play their first ever european match?",
      "option_a": "Real Madrid",
      "option_b": "Hibernians",
      "option_c": "Anderlecht",
      "option_d": "Celtic",
      "correct": "Anderlecht"
    },
    {
      "number": 40,
      "question": "Sir Bobby Charlton scored two goals in his debut against which club?",
      "option_a": "Charlton Athletic",
      "option_b": "Barnsley",
      "option_c": "Accrington Stanley",
      "option_d": "Sheffield Wednesday",
      "correct": "Charlton Athletic"
    },
    {
      "number": 41,
      "question": "United's first match at Old Trafford was against Liverpool in 1910. Liverpool won, but what was the score?",
      "option_a": "3-0",
      "option_b": "2-1",
      "option_c": "4-3",
      "option_d": "5-2",
      "correct": "4-3"
    },
    {
      "number": 42,
      "question": "Gordon Strachan scored a goal on his debut against which club?",
      "option_a": "West Ham United",
      "option_b": "Derby County",
      "option_c": "Manchester City",
      "option_d": "Watford",
      "correct": "Watford"
    },
    {
      "number": 43,
      "question": "Against which team did Sir Bobby Charlton score the most goals against as a United player?",
      "option_a": "Sheffield Wednesday",
      "option_b": "Blackpool",
      "option_c": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_d": "Wolves",
      "correct": "Tottenham Hotspur"
    },
    {
      "number": 44,
      "question": "Van Der Sar, Neville, Brown, Ferdinand, Silvestre, Ronaldo, Giggs, Ji-Sung, Rooney, Saha. Who else started the 2006 League Cup Final?",
      "option_a": "Patrice Evra",
      "option_b": "Nemanja VidiÄ",
      "option_c": "Keiran Richardson",
      "option_d": "John O'Shea",
      "correct": "John O'Shea"
    },
    {
      "number": 45,
      "question": "Sealey, Parker, Bruce, Pallister, Irwin, Kanchelskis, Keane, Giggs, Hughes, Cantona. Who else started the 1994 League Cup Final loss to Aston Villa?",
      "option_a": "Paul Ince",
      "option_b": "Gary Walsh",
      "option_c": "Lee Sharpe",
      "option_d": "Brian McClair",
      "correct": "Paul Ince"
    },
    {
      "number": 46,
      "question": "Barthez, Neville, Brown, Ferdinand, Silvestre, Beckham, Keane, Giggs, Scholes, Van Nistelrooy. Who else started the 2003 League Cup Final loss to Liverpool?",
      "option_a": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_b": "John O'Shea",
      "option_c": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_d": "Juan SebastiÃ¡n VerÃ³n",
      "correct": "Juan SebastiÃ¡n VerÃ³n"
    },
    {
      "number": 47,
      "question": "Schmeichel, Neville, Bruce, Pallister, Irwin, Ince, Keane, Sharpe, Hughes, McClair. Who else started the 1995 FA Cup Final loss against Everton?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_c": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_d": "Gary Walsh",
      "correct": "Nicky Butt"
    },
    {
      "number": 48,
      "question": "De Gea, Varela, Carrick, Blind, Herrera, Schneiderlin, Lingard, Mata, Depay, Rashford. Which player is missing from the line-up that beat Midtylland 5-1 in the Europa League?",
      "option_a": "Regan Poole",
      "option_b": "Donald Love",
      "option_c": "Paddy McNair",
      "option_d": "Joe Riley",
      "correct": "Joe Riley"
    },
    {
      "number": 49,
      "question": "Who was the first Manchester United player to score a European Cup hat-trick?",
      "option_a": "George Best",
      "option_b": "Denis Law",
      "option_c": "Tommy Taylor",
      "option_d": "Dennis Viollet",
      "correct": "Tommy Taylor"
    },
    {
      "number": 50,
      "question": "On their way to winning the 1990/91 European Cup Winners' Cup, two United players scored 4 goals. Brian McClair was one, but who was the other?",
      "option_a": "Mark Hughes",
      "option_b": "Clayton Blackmore",
      "option_c": "Lee Sharpe",
      "option_d": "Steve Bruce",
      "correct": "Steve Bruce"
    },
    {
      "number": 51,
      "question": "Manchester United signed Danish winger Jesper Olsen from Ajax in 1984. What was the fee paid for him?",
      "option_a": "Â£400,000",
      "option_b": "Â£200,000",
      "option_c": "Â£800,000",
      "option_d": "Â£350,000",
      "correct": "Â£350,000"
    },
    {
      "number": 52,
      "question": "Who were Utd's last European opponents before the English ban was placed?",
      "option_a": "FerencvÃ¡ros",
      "option_b": "Videoton",
      "option_c": "Zalaegerszeg",
      "option_d": "Debrecen",
      "correct": "Videoton"
    },
    {
      "number": 53,
      "question": "Bailey, Gidman, Albiston, Whiteside, McGrath, Moran, Robson, Strachan, Hughes, Stapleton. Which of the following also started the 1985 FA Cup final for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Jesper Olsen",
      "option_b": "Graeme Hogg",
      "option_c": "Alan Brazil",
      "option_d": "Mike Duxbury",
      "correct": "Jesper Olsen"
    },
    {
      "number": 54,
      "question": "1964-65: United played Arsenal at Old Trafford. If United won this game they would win the championship with a game in hand. What was the final scoreline?",
      "option_a": "2-0 Arsenal",
      "option_b": "3-1 United",
      "option_c": "4-2 Arsenal",
      "option_d": "4-0 United",
      "correct": "3-1 United"
    },
    {
      "number": 55,
      "question": "Who scored Manchester United's goal in the 1-0 victory over Liverpool in the 1979 FA Cup Semi-Final replay?",
      "option_a": "Martin Buchan",
      "option_b": "Jimmy Greenhoff",
      "option_c": "Lou Macari",
      "option_d": "Arthur Albiston",
      "correct": "Jimmy Greenhoff"
    },
    {
      "number": 56,
      "question": "Schmeichel, Parker, Irwin, Bruce, Pallister, Cantona, Ince, Keane, Hughes, Giggs. Which of the following also started the 1994 FA Cup final for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Lee Sharpe",
      "option_b": "Brian McClair",
      "option_c": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Andrei Kanchelskis",
      "correct": "Andrei Kanchelskis"
    },
    {
      "number": 57,
      "question": "Schmeichel, P.Nevile, Bruce, Pallister, Sharpe, Beckham, Butt, Keane, Cole, Giggs. Which of the following also started the 1995 First Round, 2nd Leg for Manchester United against Rotor Volgograd?",
      "option_a": "John O'Kane",
      "option_b": "Terry Cooke",
      "option_c": "Chris Casper",
      "option_d": "Andrei Kanchelskis",
      "correct": "John O'Kane"
    },
    {
      "number": 58,
      "question": "Dimitar Berbatov scored a hat-trick against Liverpool in 2010. Before this match the last hat-trick to be scored in a match between the two teams was in ____?",
      "option_a": "1946",
      "option_b": "1967",
      "option_c": "1970",
      "option_d": "1998",
      "correct": "1946"
    },
    {
      "number": 59,
      "question": "Sir Bobby Charlton made his final league appearance for Manchester United in 1973, but his day was spoilt by a 1-0 defeat at which ground?",
      "option_a": "Maine Road",
      "option_b": "Villa Park",
      "option_c": "Highbury",
      "option_d": "Stamford Bridge",
      "correct": "Stamford Bridge"
    },
    {
      "number": 60,
      "question": "Schmeichel, G.Nevile, P.Nevile, Pallister, May, Beckham, Butt, Keane, Scholes, Cantona. Who else started the 6-3 loss to Southampton?",
      "option_a": "Karel Poborsky",
      "option_b": "Ben Thornley",
      "option_c": "Jordi Cruyff",
      "option_d": "Brian McClair",
      "correct": "Jordi Cruyff"
    },
    {
      "number": 61,
      "question": "Gaskell, Dunne, Cantwell, Crerand, Setters, Giles, Quixall, Herd, Law, Charlton. Which of the following also started the 1963 FA Cup final for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Nobby Stiles",
      "option_b": "Shay Brennan",
      "option_c": "George Best",
      "option_d": "Bill Foulkes",
      "correct": "Bill Foulkes"
    },
    {
      "number": 62,
      "question": "Denis Law was signed from which Italian Club?",
      "option_a": "Reggina",
      "option_b": "Empoli",
      "option_c": "Sampdoria",
      "option_d": "Torino",
      "correct": "Torino"
    },
    {
      "number": 63,
      "question": "Ray Wilkins was signed from Chelsea in 1979 for how much?",
      "option_a": "Â£825,000",
      "option_b": "Â£875,000",
      "option_c": "Â£925,000",
      "option_d": "Â£985,000",
      "correct": "Â£825,000"
    },
    {
      "number": 64,
      "question": "1965: United won their sixth league title this year, but by what means?",
      "option_a": "Goal difference",
      "option_b": "Goal average",
      "option_c": "By ten points",
      "option_d": "Goals scored",
      "correct": "Goal average"
    },
    {
      "number": 65,
      "question": "1970: How many goals did George Best score in an FA Cup 5th round game, against Northampton Town on February 7th?",
      "option_a": "4",
      "option_b": "5",
      "option_c": "6",
      "option_d": "7",
      "correct": "6"
    },
    {
      "number": 66,
      "question": "Having controversially lost to Aston Villa in the 1957 FA Cup Final, League Champions Manchester United met the Cup Winners a few months later to play for the FA Charity Shield. What was the result?",
      "option_a": "Manchester United 0 Aston Villa 0",
      "option_b": "Manchester United 2 Aston Villa 1",
      "option_c": "Manchester United 1 Aston Villa 2",
      "option_d": "Manchester United 4 Aston Villa 0",
      "correct": "Manchester United 4 Aston Villa 0"
    },
    {
      "number": 67,
      "question": "On 18th January, 1958, in the last League game the Busby Babes would play in front of their adoring supporters at Old Trafford, they beat Bolton Wanderers by what score?",
      "option_a": "4-1",
      "option_b": "5-4",
      "option_c": "3-0",
      "option_d": "7-2",
      "correct": "7-2"
    },
    {
      "number": 68,
      "question": "On 25th January, 1958, in the last game the Busby Babes would play at Old Trafford, which team did United meet in the FA Cup fourth round?",
      "option_a": "Ipswich Town",
      "option_b": "Sheffield Wednesday",
      "option_c": "Bournemouth",
      "option_d": "Workington Town",
      "correct": "Ipswich Town"
    },
    {
      "number": 69,
      "question": "Which team knocked Manchester United, the defending champions, out of the European Cup in the 1968/69 season of the trophy?",
      "option_a": "Real Madrid",
      "option_b": "Waterford",
      "option_c": "Reipas Lahti",
      "option_d": "AC Milan",
      "correct": "AC Milan"
    },
    {
      "number": 70,
      "question": "Which Manchester United player was top scorer in the European Cup in the 1968/69 season of the trophy?",
      "option_a": "Nobby Stiles",
      "option_b": "George Best",
      "option_c": "Denis Law",
      "option_d": "Bobby Charlton",
      "correct": "Denis Law"
    },
    {
      "number": 71,
      "question": "The first transfer received for a player by Manchester United was for William Bryant in 1900. But how much was he sold for?",
      "option_a": "Â£20",
      "option_b": "Â£30",
      "option_c": "Â£40",
      "option_d": "Â£50",
      "correct": "Â£50"
    },
    {
      "number": 72,
      "question": "The first transfer received for a player by Manchester United was for William Bryant in 1900. But who was he sold to?",
      "option_a": "Birmingham City",
      "option_b": "Blackpool",
      "option_c": "Bolton Wanderers",
      "option_d": "Blackburn Rovers",
      "correct": "Blackburn Rovers"
    },
    {
      "number": 73,
      "question": "Kuszczak, Rafael, Vidic, Evans, Evra, Carrick, Fletcher, Park, Berbatov, Owen. Which player also started the 2010 League Cup Final?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Darren Gibson",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Antonio Valencia",
      "correct": "Antonio Valencia"
    },
    {
      "number": 74,
      "question": "Who scored the only goal for United in the 1993 Charity Shield against Arsenal?",
      "option_a": "Mark Hughes",
      "option_b": "Andrei Kanchelskis",
      "option_c": "Steve Bruce",
      "option_d": "Bryan Robson",
      "correct": "Mark Hughes"
    },
    {
      "number": 75,
      "question": "Bosnich, G Neville, Stam, Irwin, Beckham, Keane, Butt, Giggs, Scholes, Solskjaer. Which other player started the 1999 Intercontinental Cup Final?",
      "option_a": "Danny Higginbotham",
      "option_b": "Quinton Fortune",
      "option_c": "Mikael Silvestre",
      "option_d": "Phil Neville",
      "correct": "Mikael Silvestre"
    },
    {
      "number": 76,
      "question": "Schmeichel, G Neville, Pallister, May, Irwin, Butt, Keane, Giggs, Scholes, Cantona. Which other player started the 1996 FA Charity Shield?",
      "option_a": "Jordi Cryuff",
      "option_b": "Brian McClair",
      "option_c": "Karel Poborsky",
      "option_d": "David Beckham",
      "correct": "David Beckham"
    },
    {
      "number": 77,
      "question": "Schmeichel, Parker, Irwin, Bruce, Pallister, Kanchelskis, Ince, Giggs, McClair, Hughes. Who else played in the 1992 League Cup Final?",
      "option_a": "Mike Phelan",
      "option_b": "Lee Sharpe",
      "option_c": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Mark Robins",
      "correct": "Mike Phelan"
    },
    {
      "number": 78,
      "question": "Van Der Sar, G Neville, Ferdinand, Vidic, Evra, Fletcher, Scholes, Nani, Rooney, Tevez. Who else played int the 2008 UEFA Super Cup loss?",
      "option_a": "Darrem Gibson",
      "option_b": "Rodrigo Possebon",
      "option_c": "Park Ji-Sung",
      "option_d": "Anderson",
      "correct": "Anderson"
    },
    {
      "number": 79,
      "question": "De Gea, Valencia, LindelÃ¶f, Smalling, Darmian, Herrera, Matic, Pogba, Lukaku, Lingard. Who else played in the 2017 UEFA Super Cup loss?",
      "option_a": "Daley Blind",
      "option_b": "Michael Carrick",
      "option_c": "Henrikh Mkhitaryan",
      "option_d": "Marouane Fellaini",
      "correct": "Henrikh Mkhitaryan"
    },
    {
      "number": 80,
      "question": "Van Der Sar, G Neville, Ferdiand, Brown, Evra, Ronaldo, Scholes, Giggs, Rooney, Saha. Who else started the 5-1 win over Fulham on the opening day of the 2006/07 season?",
      "option_a": "John O'Shea",
      "option_b": "Park Ji-Sung",
      "option_c": "Darren fletcher",
      "option_d": "Ole Gunnar Solksjaer",
      "correct": "John O'Shea"
    },
    {
      "number": 81,
      "question": "As of December 2022, Manchester United have broken their record transfer fee 32 times. How many of those players have been Scottish?",
      "option_a": "6",
      "option_b": "9",
      "option_c": "12",
      "option_d": "15",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "number": 82,
      "question": "Against which team did Manchester United play their first League Cup game in 1960?",
      "option_a": "Exeter City",
      "option_b": "Walsall",
      "option_c": "Darwen FC",
      "option_d": "Southampton",
      "correct": "Exeter City"
    },
    {
      "number": 83,
      "question": "De Gea, Rafael, Vidic, Jones, Evra, Cleverley, Carrick, Giggs, Welbeck, Van Persie. Who else started the 2-0 win over Wigan in the 2013 FA Community Shield?",
      "option_a": "Antonio Valencia",
      "option_b": "Adnan Januzaj",
      "option_c": "Shinji Kagawa",
      "option_d": "Wilfred Zaha",
      "correct": "Wilfred Zaha"
    },
    {
      "number": 84,
      "question": "De Gea, Smalling, Ferdinand, Vidic, Evra, Nani, Carrick, Young, Rooney, Welcbeck. Who else started the 3-2 win over Manchester City in the 2011 FA Community Shield?",
      "option_a": "Park Ji-Sung",
      "option_b": "Tom Cleverley",
      "option_c": "Phil Jones",
      "option_d": "Anderson",
      "correct": "Anderson"
    },
    {
      "number": 85,
      "question": "De Gea, Jones, Ferdinand, Vidic, Evra, Carrick, Scholes, Kagawa, Van Persie, Hernandez. Who else started Sir Alex Ferguson's last game in charge at Old Trafford in a 2-1 win against Swansea?",
      "option_a": "Danny Welbeck",
      "option_b": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Antonio Valencia",
      "correct": "Danny Welbeck"
    },
    {
      "number": 86,
      "question": "Turner, Duxbury, Moran, Hogg, Albiston, McGrath, Moses, Barnes, Stapleton, Davenport. Who else started in Sir Alex Ferguson's first game in charge of Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Gary Walsh",
      "option_b": "Tony Gill",
      "option_c": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Clayton Blackmore",
      "correct": "Clayton Blackmore"
    },
    {
      "number": 87,
      "question": "Jordi Cruyff was signed from Barcelona in 1996. How much was the fee?",
      "option_a": "Â£1.1 million",
      "option_b": "Â£1.2 million",
      "option_c": "Â£1.3 million",
      "option_d": "Â£1.4 million",
      "correct": "Â£1.4 million"
    },
    {
      "number": 88,
      "question": "Kleberson scored two goals in his Manchester United career. Against which two teams were his goals?",
      "option_a": "Blackburn Rovers & Everton",
      "option_b": "Charlton Athletic & Southampton",
      "option_c": "Birmingham City & Middlesbrough",
      "option_d": "Leeds United and Fulham",
      "correct": "Blackburn Rovers & Everton"
    },
    {
      "number": 89,
      "question": "Schmeichel, P Neville, Bruce, Pallister, G Neville, Butt, Keane, Giggs, Cole, Cantona. Who else started the 2-2 draw against Liverpool in Cantona's return from his suspension from his kung-fu kick?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "David Beckham",
      "option_c": "Paul Parker",
      "option_d": "Lee Sharpe",
      "correct": "Lee Sharpe"
    },
    {
      "number": 90,
      "question": "Who scored the winner as Manchester United beat Liverpool in the 1977 FA Cup final?",
      "option_a": "Jimmy Greenhoff",
      "option_b": "Stuart Pearson",
      "option_c": "Lou Macari",
      "option_d": "Steve Coppell",
      "correct": "Jimmy Greenhoff"
    },
    {
      "number": 91,
      "question": "How many goals did Manchester United score on their way to winning the 1968 European Cup?",
      "option_a": "13",
      "option_b": "14",
      "option_c": "15",
      "option_d": "16",
      "correct": "16"
    },
    {
      "number": 92,
      "question": "How many goals did Manchester United score on their way to winning the 1991 European Cup Winners' Cup?",
      "option_a": "17",
      "option_b": "18",
      "option_c": "19",
      "option_d": "20",
      "correct": "17"
    },
    {
      "number": 93,
      "question": "Manchester United won their 5th FA Cup in 1983. But who did they beat in the 4th round 2-0 on the way to that victory?",
      "option_a": "Watford",
      "option_b": "Burnley",
      "option_c": "Stoke City",
      "option_d": "Luton Town",
      "correct": "Luton Town"
    },
    {
      "number": 94,
      "question": "Foster, O'Shea, Ferdinand, Evans, Evra, Ronaldo, Scholes, Nani, Welbeck, Tevez. Who else started the 2009 League Cup Final win over Tottenham Hotspur?",
      "option_a": "Anderson",
      "option_b": "Darren Gibson",
      "option_c": "Park Ji-Sung",
      "option_d": "Ryan Giggs",
      "correct": "Darren Gibson"
    },
    {
      "number": 95,
      "question": "How many goals did Manchester United score on their way to winning the 2009 League Cup?",
      "option_a": "11",
      "option_b": "13",
      "option_c": "15",
      "option_d": "17",
      "correct": "13"
    },
    {
      "number": 96,
      "question": "By what margin did Manchester United win the 1956-57 Football League title?",
      "option_a": "2",
      "option_b": "4",
      "option_c": "6",
      "option_d": "8",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "number": 97,
      "question": "By what margin did Manchester United win the 1966-67 Football League title?",
      "option_a": "2",
      "option_b": "4",
      "option_c": "6",
      "option_d": "8",
      "correct": "4"
    },
    {
      "number": 98,
      "question": "Manchester United won their 7th League title in the 1966/1967 Football League season. Who finished 2nd that season?",
      "option_a": "Nottingham Forest",
      "option_b": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_c": "Leeds United",
      "option_d": "Liverpool",
      "correct": "Nottingham Forest"
    },
    {
      "number": 99,
      "question": "Which player scored United's only goal as they won the 1997 Charity Shield on penalties after a 1-1 draw?",
      "option_a": "Gary Pallister",
      "option_b": "Gary Neville",
      "option_c": "Jordi Cruyff",
      "option_d": "Ronny Johnsen",
      "correct": "Ronny Johnsen"
    },
    {
      "number": 100,
      "question": "After 26 years, Manchester United finally ended their English League title drought by winning the 1992/93 Premier League title. But who finished 2nd that season?",
      "option_a": "Blackburn Rovers",
      "option_b": "Norwich City",
      "option_c": "Queens Park Rangers",
      "option_d": "Aston Villa",
      "correct": "Aston Villa"
    },
    {
      "number": 101,
      "question": "United last won the title in the 2012-13 season. How many goals did we concede that season?",
      "option_a": "34",
      "option_b": "39",
      "option_c": "37",
      "option_d": "43",
      "correct": "43"
    },
    {
      "number": 102,
      "question": "Schmeichel, May, Bruce, Pallister, Sharpe, Kanchelskis, McClair, Ince, Giggs, Cantona. Who else started the 1994 Charity Shield that we won 2-0?",
      "option_a": "Dion Dublin",
      "option_b": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_c": "Keith Gillespie",
      "option_d": "Mark Hughes",
      "correct": "Mark Hughes"
    },
    {
      "number": 103,
      "question": "Howard, Neville, Silvestre, O'Shea, Fortune, Bellion, Keane, Giggs, Scholes, Smith. Who else started the 2004 Community Shield against Arsenal?",
      "option_a": "Eric Djemba-Djemba",
      "option_b": "Kieran Richardson",
      "option_c": "Chris Eagles",
      "option_d": "Darren Fletcher",
      "correct": "Eric Djemba-Djemba"
    },
    {
      "number": 104,
      "question": "Which United player finshed 2nd in the PFA Players' Player of the Year in the 1992-93 Premier League season?",
      "option_a": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_b": "Paul Ince",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Mark Hughes",
      "correct": "Paul Ince"
    },
    {
      "number": 105,
      "question": "Which team did Manchester United beat 2-0 in the 2nd qualifying round to progress to the 1998/1999 Champions League group stage?",
      "option_a": "ObiliÄ",
      "option_b": "LKS Lodz",
      "option_c": "FC Metz",
      "option_d": "Rosenborg",
      "correct": "LKS Lodz"
    },
    {
      "number": 106,
      "question": "Schmeichel, G Neville, Johnsen, Stam, Irwin, Beckham, Keane, Butt, Yorke, Cole. Which player also started the thrilling 3-2 win in the 2nd Leg of the semi-final against Juventus in the Champions League?",
      "option_a": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_b": "Jesper Blomqvist",
      "option_c": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_d": "Phil Neville",
      "correct": "Jesper Blomqvist"
    }
  ]
}
